let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "Who was Thomas Jefferson's childhood best friend?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "George Washington",
        choiceB: "John Adams",
        choiceC: "The Marquis de Lafayette",
        choiceD: "Dabney Carr",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "What was Thomas Jefferson's wife's name?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Louisa",
        choiceB: "Martha",
        choiceC: "Dolly",
        choiceD: "Elizabeth",
        correct: "B"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "Which college did Jefferson graduate from?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Yale",
        choiceB: "Harvard",
        choiceC: "The College of William and Mary",
        choiceD: "St. John's College",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "In Virginia, June 1774, To show solidarity with other colonies and to protest the Boston Port Act, a day of ____ was declared ",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Fasting",
        choiceB: "Rioting",
        choiceC: "Silence",
        choiceD: "War preperation",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "In August 1774, Jefferson published  ___",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "The Declaration of Independence",
        choiceB: "A Summary View of the Rights of British America",
        choiceC: "Constitution of the United States",
        choiceD: "Common Sense",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "What year did Jefferson first get elected to Governor of Virginia?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "1765",
        choiceB: "1770",
        choiceC: "1776",
        choiceD: "1779",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "In 1784, Jefferson becomes the forgein minister to which country?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "France",
        choiceB: "England",
        choiceC: "Russia",
        choiceD: "Spain",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "What was Jefferson's role in Washington's presidency?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Vice President",
        choiceB: "Secretary of War",
        choiceC: "Treasury Dept.",
        choiceD: "Secretary of State",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "What was Jefferson's role in the Adams presidency?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Vice President",
        choiceB: "Secretary of War",
        choiceC: "Treasury Dept",
        choiceD: "Secretary of State",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "What was the name of Thomas Jefferson's Home?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Montecito",
        choiceB: "Mount Vernon",
        choiceC: "Monticello",
        choiceD: "Montpelier",
        correct: "C"
    }
];